

+1 (778) 855-6870 sbagga@sfu.ca sandybagga.com

SKILLS

Experience Design
UX/UI Design
Interaction Design
Visual Design
Prototyping
Brand Strategy
User Testing

TOOLS

Adobe CC

Figma

Sketch

ProtoPie

Keynote

VS Code

Pen + Paper

INTERESTS

Jazz-Fusion Music Shred Guitar Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu World Religions Stand-Up Comedy Mindfulness

SOCIAL

Video Games





sandybagga95

Sandy Bagga

An experience designer building meaningful narratives

I'm a senior design student based in Vancouver, BC. I'm interested in brand strategy, user journeys, and product design. I think interactions with an ecosystem of apps, products, and services can and should be analysed from a psychological perspective.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Learning Support Worker

Amazing Tutors Children's Foundation / Feb 2019 - present

Gaining deep understanding of student needs to ensure that the best possible support is delivered Building and maintaining relationships with students, making a genuine investment in their success Coordinating with other staff to ensure that students are receiving adequate and appropriate support

UX/UI Designer - Intern

Visier Inc. / Jan 2017 - Aug 2017

Designed and delivered a critical user experience during a transition to a new visual design language Generated visual elements (icons, toasts, etc.) in Illustrator for the reimagined design styleguide Implemented an atomized approach to UI design in Sketch that streamlined developer handoff

Web Development + SEO - Intern

Brixwork Real Estate Marketing / May 2016 - Aug 2016

Designed, implemented, and shipped multiple lead generation projects

Maintained search engine optimization campaigns for all clients

Formulated a system to make the designer-to-developer handoff more efficient

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Composer

Live from the Olive Garden / 2019

I am part of a group called 'Live from the Olive Garden' and our eponymous debut EP is available to stream and download. The album as part of a course project, and its reception led us to continue.

Graphic Designer - Volunteer

SFU Jazz Band Club / Ongoing

Design and deliver print + digital materials (programs, posters, social media banners) for the semester-end concert to suit the event's motif, the last one being a Saul Bass-inspired jungle theme

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Science / Spring 2020 School of Interactive Arts + Technology

Berklee College of Music

Guitar Sessions / Summer 2013
Berklee Summer Programs